- You look like you've lost weight since I last saw you.
- Me?
No, i'm not.
Didn't you want to have the wedding at church because of family reasons?
I think she's very confused. You need to help her at this kind of situation.
A person who is not honest is the type of person I hate the most.
It's a misunderstanding
If you didn't want to get married why didn't you say so?
It's not that I don't like it.
You know what your mother said to me?
She asked me if I have family reasons. It means we look poor.
I can endure anything but not this one.
You have the air of the rich.
Thank you, that's so comforting.
Why are you yelling at her? What did she do wrong?
You are the one who changed your mind!
Hae Jung Hoon!
I won't let anyone treat my woman this way!
How could you do such a thing?
That's what you wanted.
Now how am I supposed to face your mother?
Hey, what are you doing here?
Where is Hae Yoon?
Want to have a drink with me?
-Who is he?
- Mom.
Who are you?
It's just a sunbae
Episode 5
- You must be hungry.
- I'm okay.
I'll make you ramen.
My apartment was robbed.
My mom left.
What's that?
Woah
Your wife!
Oh, my back hurts.
- Hey, I want water too.
- You're up?
You should've woke up earlier. I had to carry you all the way here.
If you had known I wasn't drunk, you would've told me to go home.
- No wonder why you were drunk so quickly.
- Can't really see Mom today.
Then why did you defend a woman in front of your mom?
I didn't want to, just that Hye Yoon is weak.
She has to go through this because of me. Besides, Mom has Dad.
I don't understand why people argue when preparing for a wedding.
You guys don't fight?
It's like a business. We just have to satisfy what we want for each other.
I'm happy when I'm with Hae Yoon.
But if we decide to do something together, it's so hard to negotiate.
If you guys do that,
it's going to be tough until you really get married.
I have to relax heyin and my mom
I feel like im gonna die
-Is that your fiance? -No, she doesn't have my door code.
Ya!
Dong Bi,
Oh I see you again. I have to talk to this jerk.
I'm leaving Hyung
I heard you're getting married!
You can't marry the girl you've been dating for five years
but you marry a girl you've only met a few times?
I'm too ashamed to admit I even dated you!
Stop it.
You - do you know which household's daughter I am?
If you knew you would definitely be shocked.
If you know who my father is, you will see me different.
You're so materialistic!
I should really change my door code.
I don't like this either
but I couldn't just not do anything.
The man I love is marrying another woman! What kind of mess is this
Get up, I'll take you home.
No, I'm going to sleep here. - You can't. Go back home.
I don't want to!
You're so strong.
Did you see a ghost? Why are you so startled?
I was wrong.
I was truly wrong. - About what?
I shouldn't have talked to you that way
So you already knew it, were you just with heyin?
No because I was like that to you I was scared so I came
I've never seen you that mad
I had a right to be mad, so where are you coming from?
Gijung hyung's house
They might compare you to heyin in their family
What is there to compare?
You know how my sister is.
Do you know how stressed I've been for Ki Joon's wedding and you?
Then don't meet her, you'll be less stressed.
How can I not meet her? Don't talk to me in front of Hae Yoon.
It's so embarrassing, really.
Do you think Hae Yoon's going to listen if I say something to her from now on?
Are you going to yell at her again?
I can't yell at her again? - You can yell at her.
If you have to, then you should!
I even called off the wedding before because of you.
Lets just do it.
Mom, can't we get married at a hotel?
Son I'll tell you a secret,
We couldn't get the hotel
Why didn't you tell the truth?
We would look too bad
There's a difference between having a choice and not having any
So that's why I pretended not to have a choice
Today is not my day.
Hey Stop that!
I guess you're a human too. I didn't know you would walk me home.
So who's your dad? Which company is he at?
My dad's company? It's Apple!
Aigoo~why did I even ask?
Are you just gonna leave?
Your really drunk
Yeah i'm really drunk
Sleep.
Don't make me the bad guy.
But you are a bad guy.
I'm sorry. - About what?
For being a bad guy.
You can come back to me anytime.
Even when you think it's too late, come.
- Sorry. - Oh no, it's because I didn't know.
Go back safely. - Yes
Do you like the bike that much?
- I'll go back now. - Noona, have a conscience!
Don't you see I came here during my sleep time?
You should buy me something to drink at least.
Where should I buy it?
Let's go.
You're not getting on? - I'm getting on.
-What are you doing? - What do you mean, what am I doing? Then should I fall off and die?
Ok, I've got it. Hold on tight.
You are so heavy.
Don't you think your head is too big?
You're son mean. How can you say that?
Get your big head off me!
You can call me big head.
I think you are a little crazy.
Lady is this your's?
It's really nice. Let us ride it.
- No, you can't. - Don't be like that and let us ride it once, ok?
I said you can't.
-No wonder you're so ugly.
-Ugly women have bad temper.
-I guess my mom was right.
Hey, stop there. What school do you go to?
Hey, they're in high school.
Even North Koreans can't invade us because of them.
It's nothing, just go. Go ahead.
You guys are such...
Those bastards! You guys don't respect adults!
Are you ok?
I yell at them instead of you.
You're so pathetic.
Why? Do you want to get beaten up by a highschooler?
Why do you think that?
We can beat them up.
I hate violence. I'm not a savage like you.
If I talk to you ever again, I'm not human.
Don't ever think about it.
Are you really going to leave me here?
Hey, hey, Deul Rae!
Lee Deul Rae! I don't have my wallet with me!
I don't have any money!
Give me 10,000 won!
What do you want?
How did I get home?
How would I know? You should know.
I blacked out.
Come and make me ramyun.
Hey, do I look like a fool?
I can't believe you made me do this.
I think I deserve this.
Who was with you when you had a fight with Hae Yoon?
-When Hae Yoon was...
-Shut up.
It's was the housekeeper made. Not my mom.
I like your housekeeper's kimchi better than your mom's.
It's a like that you blacked out, isn't it?
Yeah. I was so lonely when I woke up.
There was nobody home.
Then you come to my mind.
Just give up on him.
If I give up on him, then is not love.
You got a problem.
Do you think only I have a problem?
I think you two have one too.
Did you have a fight with her, didn't you?
You are right. We keep fighting.
She got mad yesterday.
She's probably wont answer my phone calls
I don't know if we can ever enter the wedding hall.
Leave it up to me.
I saw Jung Hoon with another woman.
What?!
What do you mean he was with another woman?
Do you even care? You fight all the time.
No, we don't.
What's this? Did you guys fool me?
Stop fighting. I'm leaving now, ill leave this house for you two
You can't fight in here or make out.
I'll kill you if I see you doing it
And the password is my birthday.
You said you wanted to break up with me,
but were you worried if I was with another woman?
I couldn't even imagine you being with another woman than me
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you think she would really kill us if we make out?
You know how to play with a man.
This isn't enough.
No wonder why I love you.
You got a good idea to make me come back.
Wake me up in half an hour.
I have to go somewhere.
Set an alarm. I also have to go somewhere.
How many faces do you have?
How could you do that with that innocent face?
If a mouse is driven into a corner it can bite a cat.
I think I underestimate you.
When we met for the first time, I started the background check on you.
The password was my husband's birthday.
I told you not to mess up with me. I've lived with him for seven years.
My son's future depends on me. It's about life and death.
It's not important whether I love him or not.
- What have you planned?
- You don't need to know that.
- Do you want me to back off?
- It's up to you. It's your life.
Are you going to do this again?
I told you that there were many women like you around him.
I don't fight with every single one of them. If you don't mess with me, I don't either.
You should apologize for talking shit about my background.
I am sorry.
This is my last advice. Don't date a married man.
To a married man, his wife is like his mom.
He will come back when I call him even if he plays outside.
- Thank you for the advice.
- Delete my phone number from your phone.
You appearing as a friend recommendation on my phone, it's burdensome.
I wanted to come here before the wedding.
My name is Peter.
I like baptismal names.
If I a new name I think I'd feel like a new person
What's your mom's catholic name?/Stellar
Your dad's?/Silvano
I also want one/ Hey don't get so excited over a name
No I want to go to this church together
With the people I love and family
I'm really touched
I think it would be good to get married here too.
Do I need healthcare for my face?
Huh?
No, why?
Somebody told me I look gaunt with worries.
- I think she's jealous of you.
- I know, right?
Let's get ready we shouldn't be late to th
Alright.
I told my sister to book a wedding hall at Palace Hotel.
- Don't overdo it.
- I need to overdo it.
I don't want Hae Yoon's mom to look down on me.
But that doesn't mean we have to have a wedding at a hotel.
She made me feel like that.
Who is it?
Mom and Dad. We're here.
I have a good eye sight. I see you are here.
I have something to say to you.
You should make it quick because we have to go somewhere. Come here.
Mom, Dad, I'm sorry
Doesn't Hae Yoon have a mouth?
- Honey, it's not her time to say.
- Is it?
We'll have our wedding at church.
I can't say so sure that I'll have a religion.
We wanted to pick a place that you would like
You did pick a good place, thank you
Did you speak to your mother too?
I thought it would be more important to tell you first
once you've told your mother then come too me again
There's no need mom
We've already decided to do it
Mom Dad thanks for raising me until now
Marriage is a first step in getting independent from parents
please help us start out
That's a good idea. No matter what we will support you
It seems like they had too many good things to say
What stuff?
you need money to live on your own, but Junghoon has no money
In the end, it's all coming out of our bank accounts
When I am the one who's paying, it's not easy not to interfere
Don't open your bank account to Junghoon
If we don't support him, how will they get married?
We've already agreed we'll find a way
It will have to be a loan then. If they get a loan, they have to pay interest too
Junghoon cannot make ends meet with his paycheck
Yeah sis we're here
There's a spot? Alright thanks
There's a spot at the hotel
Didn't you hear what they said earlier they want to get married at the cathedral
It is true that we asked to have the wedding at the cathedral
But the situation has changed now.
That's my mom trying to tempt you. Don't fall for it
What did we say? We asked them to follow our decisions
We could change it again
Let's reconsider
Do you really want to?
I don't want to be like that we should ignore your mother like that
You're right.
I knew it was tommorow
Mom ,lets' just have the wedding at the hotel.
-Look at this.
I'm wondering what else Hye Yoon's mom has to say.
I'm the person who made an appointment through call a few days ago.
What's your name?
-Jung Hye Jin.
I didn't have a chance to eat lunch because I had too much work to do
This is a downside to having so many clients.
-It's fine
First, let's do a provisional seizure on the real estate properties.
you can do that first?
Of course, that's the basic.
We have to do a provisional seizure before the lawsuit is initiated. That way, he can't hide his assets.
You just have to trust me.
-Okay.
You need to get evidence of his affair, without him knowing.
You have to do that personally yourself. Can you do it?
I can.
This part is a little rougher.
Oh, what's up?
I have a favor to ask, Do Hyun.
What is it?
Please set up a meal for me and Deulrae
What exactly is your relationship to Deulrae? Why are you tagging her along?
She's old. There is nothing more pitiful for a woman than being old
She's acting all haughty because she's never been married. But that's just on the paper, from appearance, she doesn't look it
You're no different
I have a building under my name
For man, being old is not pitiful. Being poor is
I don't want to. I am not in good terms with my wife recently. I don't want to ask her for a favor
When did I ask you to ask her for a favor? I said I just want to have dinner together
Dad, eat. I eat well by myself too.
Isn't that right, mommy?
-That's right.
Are you leaving for a business trip again?
-I'm not.
Aren't you glad? Since Dad's not going on a business trip?
Yes.
-Thanks for inviting me to your family's dinner.
You are the main reason for this dinner. -What do you mean?
Hello Noona!
Hye Jin, have you been well?
- Yes, you should eat.
I have to. Tae won aren't you going to greet me?
Hello.
I haven't seen you in a while. I should give you some allowance.
Thank you.
That's too much for a kid.
Noona, the more money, the more happy the kid will be.
She's older?
I've been exhausted since I met her.
Do you think you're the only one who's tired? Seriously, makes me lose my appetite.
I'm done eating so I'm leaving first.
See you next time. -Noona, you can't leave like this.
Why is he like that to our aunt? He doesn't like her by chance, does he?
He doesn't think women over the age of 20 are women. Don't worry.
It's just new to him. Being unmarried in her 50s. That's something new
Yeah, I guess so. A player couldn't even dream of dating a woman like her.
Did you only say that for me?
-Am I wrong? I guess you're still human.
Noona!
I'm going crazy.
I was sorry.
-I get it, so don't lay a finger on me.
You are unmarried at your age because you act this way
I guess being married twice is something to brag about.
It is, because of it I learned so many things.
You get divorced because you try to learn things once you're married, those things that even people who didn't get married know.
No matter how angry you are, don't comment on my flaw
If you're proud to have been married twice,
you should be proud of being divorced twice as well. Why is that a flaw?
I probably learned a bit because I got divorced too.
That's true.
what?
I'm saying you're right. Why couldn't I think of that?
Being divorced is something that I could be proud of too. I've been divorced twice
You're quite naive
Everyone tells me that. Naive. It's nice to look at, no?
I brought my motorcycle here, I'll take you home.
I am telling you in advance to avoid any misunderstanding. Don't like me because I am acting like this.
I am naturally kind person
They even give you presents!
-It's like we are really getting married.
Did you make an appointment with a specific wedding planner?
I had an appoint with Shin Misook
Oh, are you Jung Hyewon?
I am Shin Misook who gave you a call yesterday
Where are you having your wedding?
-At a hotel.
If you have wedding at a hotel, you could save on shoot, wedding dress and make up cost
What's that?
It's a wedding dress makeup shoot.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Because hotel has a better lighting, it makes you prettier so you don't have to spend as much on make up and wedding dress
That exactly what I am saying
How much is it?
You can see if you look here, but it costs from 2,000,000 - 3,000,000 won.
It's expensive.
-If you think this is expensive, then the situation becomes difficult.
It'll cost more if you prepare if personally yourself.
Okay. Let's get up.
You're leaving without a reserveration? There isn't many time left!
We will look around first
Group purchase is usually cheaper, let's just do it here.
That's right. Exactly what I'm saying.
After we think about it. We'll give you a call.
Just make a reservation. It's better if you don't have to think about it.
I thought about it and I think we don't have to spend money on shoot, wedding dress and make up
Why?
-We have Dong Bi.
I think it looks old fashioned.
-It doesn't.
Should I help you?
I was bored waiting so I think after I take the pictures choosing it later would be better.
That would be great. You're definitely intelligent.
Sekyung, this the president of a wedding magazine
Not a president
you'll be one soon
She's a reporter with a very good sense. She will be here to observe
Let me try Vera Wangs.
Alright. It's simple so it could make your body line stand out more.
Ki Joong.
Why are you here?
Do you know this person?
You have a lot of connections! How do you know him?
You know my cousin? She's his friend.
I will change and come out.
Can you act like you know me?
So? We know each other.
Wow.
-What are you doing here?
I am here to observe for the wedding magazine. The shop owner here is investing in the magazine.
Do well. I know you'll do well.
This dress is nice also.
You're not taking pictures this time?
I will.
Dong Bi is such a good friend, even letting us go to her house.
That's why I dislike Ki Joong more.
It's like we're really living together.
Instead of spending money eating out, my idea to have our date here was a good idea, wasn't it?
Okay, good job.
Honey.
I'm from a poor family, your room is bigger than my living room.
I know.
You and my finances
No, to be more specific. Because of our familie's financial difference, I'm not going to feel taken aback.
Alright.
My family's finances are
I gave all my salary as a teacher to mom and got allowance from her
When I asked my mom to give it to me for my marriage,
It turns out she spent it all on living expenses.
Our family's wealth isn't that outstanding either.
I don't know too well but I know that we own a building in Sadang-dong
But, my parents said they are all donating it, so there is no point knowing about it
Both you and me, we are poor.
The reason why I'm saying this, I think we're going to have to spend more money in the future.
Even if I can't match your wealth, I ask for your understanding.
But, when we get married, I'll be earning money so we'll be fine.
my mom's not the type to say something about money. Don't worry about it
My mom is sensitive about money, because she doesn't have any.
Then my parents can spend more money.
It's not like we are doing business.
You don't have to pay the same amount.
I calculated how much we can make. If we add our monthly salary, it's 4,000,000 won.
If we can save 70% of it,
which is about three million,
and if we save save it for three years,
it adds up to 100,000,000.
We can make 100,000,000 in three years.
Can we live with one million won?
We can if we don't have any depts. Aren't your parents going to pay for our house?
They don't tell me about that yet. My mom is meeting your mom. So they will talk about it.
I'm here, Ms Hae.
Come here.
Are we having lunch here?
This restaurants bean noodle is really famous.
Beans are very good for women at our age.
It's probably the same anywhere.
You won't say that after you eat it.
It's all organic.
So delicious.
Let's just go to another restaurant.
You should come here with someone you are very close with.
We can be close to each other. Let;s go on a trip together or something.
- Isn't it delicious?
- Yeah, it's delicious.
As long as the food is good, then it's good. I don't care about the design of the restaurant.
Is she saying this because i told her she should come with someone that's close to her?
How did you book the hotel?
I thought it's all booked.
My sister has connections to that hotel.
I see.
How many guest are there for you?
There won't be that many.
i'm only going to invite people who can really bless the wedding of Jung Hoon.
That's good. Since there aren't that many guests coming, it will cost less.
It was difficult enough to reserve a wedding hall, if he cost of the wedding runs too high, it will be too burdensome for you
what is she talking about? she wants us to foot the whole bill?
cost wise, it will be equal for you and me. What do you mean buy too much of a burden?
what?
Why are you so surprised?
I thought the groom is paying for the rental cost of the wedding hall
It was to my knowledge that the wedding hall rental cost is split equally between the groom and the bride
it wasn't like that for my eldest daughter. my son-in-law paid footed the whole bill. So I assumed that was the case
That's because that was his second marriage
As you've heard from Junghoon, we're not well off
we don't care about such things. the most important thing is individual's character
with my budget, I can't afford to have the wedding at a hotel
if that's the case, we will pay for the cost
will that be okay?
what can I do? You said you can't afford it
Thank you. in-law
She's such a thief after only feeding me soybean noodles for a meal
have you met my mother-in-law?
You're not even married yet and how can mother-in-law roll off your tongue so easily like that?
what is my mother upset about?
did you know that we have to foot the whole bill for wedding hall rental?
I didn't know.
I think that was her original intention from the get go. I feel uneasy whenever I meet her
Hey Yoon's family is not well off. I am sure they didn't plan on this from the beginning
She's like a thief, exactly like a thief.
That's good. Number of wedding guests will be similar to ours. That should lower the cost of the wedding
It was hard enough reserving the wedding hall. If the cost of wedding runs too high, that will be too burdensome for you.
This was most certainly planned all along
What's going on?
The more I think about Hyeyun's mom, the more angry I get
She wants to get her daughter married off for free
If you decided to accept her terms, just accept it without further complaint
Everyone knows it was Hyeyoon's older sister's husband's second marriage
He married a younger woman who's never been married before. Of course he should have paid for everything. But that's not the case for my Junghoon
It seems like you care about money after all
No I am not. It's not just about the money. How Hyeyoon's mom acts gets on my nerves
She doesn't feel apologetic at all
So if she acts timid because she feels apologetic, do you think you will like that?
That would get on my nerves too. How in the world did we end up being in laws with such family. I have to worry about all sorts of things
Let's sleep. Worrying will only age you
I will never meet Hyeyoon's mom to talk about wedding again
After seeing the house the in-laws provide, I will have to buy the appliances. Let's leave it at $5,000 for now
dowry and everything, I'll try to keep it under $10,000
Before I go to bed I wanted to check. Mother-in-law was happy to pay for the rental of wedding hall?
yes she did. She has an innocent side to her
When she was young she had her parents then her husband after getting married. She lived a sheltered life
Her life is so different from yours considering you're both women
There are pro and cons to everything
There is no point of thinking the grass is greener on the other side
It's best to live you life the way you do
What is that?
They gave me this as a gift when I went to a wedding convention. I watered it so it would grow
If you water it too much, it will die
it can't die
I'm going to take it with me when I'm married. It'll be going in my - I mean, our room.
What kind of place are your in-laws buying you?
You didn't talk about it with my mother-in-law today?
I didn't. We had bean noodles today.
You took her to eat bean noodles?!
That's right, I can't?
You don't care about formalities? You're not even close to her yet and you treated her to soy bean noodles?
Why are you getting angry about this? What's wrong with the soy bean noodle? Even kings had it
Then let the king have it. You should have treated mother-in-law to something different
Oh I'm really unsatisfied, really!
I can't even treat her what I would like to treat her?
She's no help. How can one say no when someone else is paying for it. Of course she would say yes
－Yes Mother. - It's late, isn't it?
It's okay, Mother.
I wanted to tell you this tonight. Come to my place tomorrow.
Yes, I understand.
Ah, it's the bean noodles.
You must be tired. I prepared your bath with some oils.
What are you planning?
Let's have a drink later. I'll prepare it.
Cheers.
Instead of fighting, I wanted to have a truthful conversation.
Even if we end up divorcing, let's keep it amicable
that's what I was about to say. Let's have a frank conversation
I told you last time, a man doesn't cheat for no reason.
it's because the wife didn't satisfy the husband.
when a man is upset, he could say anything
Was there somewhere I was lacking towards you as a wife?
No, you weren't lacking in anything. You were the perfect wife -too perfect. That much I admit.
So then why did you cheat?
There's an animal that lives inside me.
So, it wasn't my mistake?
No, it's my problem.
From what I know, the woman you're having an affair right now. She's the third woman, am I right?
If you take out one night, yeah.
Do you even want a divorce?
Not really, what about you?
Me?
I want it.
When you weren't home, being home alone with Tae Won was nice.
I didn't know before, without you I could be so happy.
Then why'd you come back.
To get a divorce. I have to show Tae Won a divorce that's settled.
So he won't get hurt as much.
What kind of show is this?
Was I lacking as a wife for you?
No, you weren't lacking in anything. You were the perfect wife-too perfect. That much I admit.
Then why'd you cheat?
There's an animal inside me, that's why.
Have a seat.
-Would you like some tea? -I'll have water, please.
Bring us some water and tea.
-Yes.
I called you here today because I have a request.
I heard about your family's difficult financial problems. I confirmed with your mom yesterday also.
I'll give up everything else, but I want you to know this.
The wedding gift. Please understand.
I'm telling you beforehand because it's important.
Can you keep the favor?
Why are you not answering? I'll say it again.
-I'll try my best, mother.
I know you may feel bad but it's better than talking behind your back.
I wish to be more honest with each other in the future.
I understand.
Since Ki Joon is getting married the same month as Jung Hoon,
I keep comparing.
Of course I am not materialistic enough to hang on to those things. Nevertheless, it is on my mind
I understand, mother.
Do you? Then that's a relief. Honestly, your mothe-
No.
Anyways, my sister and I are close but,
She got jealous of me since I was young.
Are you not like that with your sister?
Yes. Even though our age difference isn't big, she's warm and like a mom to me.
What you're saying right now is insensitive.
I just talked down on my sister but you talk warmly about your sister.
Then what does that make me?
I got caught again.
You can just say that your sister was fine.
I only said that because I wanted to be honest with you.
You've always been candid with me, but I don't think I was candid with you.
To get closer with you, that's why I said it honestly.
I'm sorry.
-It was like that?
Then I was wrong on this part.
You came quickly.
It didn't take long from there. I didn't know it'd be this close.
What's gotten into you? wanting to see me like this
I came all the way here, it'd be rude for me to just leave.
Before, you just left. That time I was sad.
- So that's why I came. - Have a seat. I made cookies.
Take them with you. I made them for you.
- Would you like a latte? - You can make that too?
Should I buy you a coffee machine for your wedding?
It can even make espresso well.
It's okay. I have moka express stovetop espresso maker
you and your peculiar tastes
- Unni, what about yours? - I just have regular coffee.
Thank you.
For what?
You always yielded to me.
I got to go to school. And you couldn't go because of me.
For our family expenses, I had to make it to public (in-state) university. My scores weren't that good
You studied better than I did.
Still I studied to be a caregiver.
So I became a wife.
There are many graduates from Seoul National University who are unable to become doctor's wife.
So, are you happy about your marriage?
Why do you ask?
I don't understand why it is so difficult to get married when everyone else gets married
my mother-in-law isn't same as before either. Before, she was endlessly generous and understanding
but she's no longer the same. I'm in awe of how you make your household run smoothly like this
I am jealous of you.
Everyone has a warm love story of how they got married.
How they met, what they had to go through to get married
I didn't think about love,
I thought about whether Do Hyun could take care of me or not.
But Hye Yoon, even so, I loved your brother-in-law.
If I could have been with him, I was willing to give up my life
I know it was difficult since your relationship started off with moral flaw
but you need to get over that issue now
nothing is more important than love in a marriage
You are way better than others who stay married for convenience even when they don't love each other
If you need help with wedding preparations, let me know. I will prepare it for you.
Unni, what did you do for the wedding gift (dowry)?
I just skipped it. If nothing else, I should have well prepared the wedding gift (dowry)
I feel like my in-laws say something about it time after time
my in-laws are not the type to do so
That's what you think
Preparing for a wedding is the beginning of marriage
Junghoon has been affluent generation to generation
Don't start off in unequal footing
Give what needs to be given and receive what need to be received
It's neater that way
-The photos came out well. -They did, right? I told you the photographer is good.
She's not a photographer but she's really good with editing too
Hello.
good to see you mini reporter. You must be busy
A little bit. Have you not decided on a dress yet?
yes, I am here to discuss with the shop owner about my engagement party dress
You're doing an engagement as well?
I'm doing it. What others do, I have to do it as well.
So that's why I'm asking, can't you take my engagement photos?
There are professional reporters but
I would like someone who knew our love story well.
Thanks for the offer, but I will have to decline. I've been very busy with other work.
What if I were to invest in your start-up?
The preparations are complete.
I better try it on
You are free now. Can you take picture like you did before? I would like to look at them
She gets what she wants
Just say yes if it's not too much trouble. She will be helpful for your future too
I am leaving
Didn't you hear her asking for you to take pictures?
Please tell her I find her unpleasant
Mini reporter
hey, please hurry
You're here again? you seem to ride motorcycle often
I wonder how much longer I have to ride motorcycle with two people protecting me
Until you're good at it
That's the answer. Until she's good at it. I will be on the lookout today
okay, you become 2nd, since you're not good
I know my place too
Let's go.
Oh no!
It's blood, oh no, what do we do now?
Are you ok?
I don't think I broke any bones
How can you stop there like that? He got hurt because of you
What did I do?
Of course he thought you're crossing but you stopped
He didn't have enough space to safely hit the brakes. So he sacrificed himself because he was afraid of colliding into you
Is that it?
It's her fault really
to be strictly speaking, it's your fault. You were supposed to look out for traffic
You should have calculated enough time for 3 motorcycles to cross
Hyung, that's not it
I crossed before the traffic light changed
Even if the traffic light changed, if she had crossed, you'd have crossed too
then all of us would have crossed. It wasn't my fault for not being a proper lookout
Be quiet. My head is bleeding
I am sorry. I am sorry
don't cry. it's okay
Do you really want to argue who's right in situations like this?
Why are you yelling at me?
what can we do?
It's ok, don't cry.
what can I do? It was my fault
What is that you need to give me?
My sister baked these for you
this tastes so good. How can this be so good? Are you this good too?
I could do it if I have the recipe. There is no reason why I can't
Smart woman is a good cook
such spirit! I want to get married quickly and eat what you put on the table
get dressed if you washed up. aren't you going to work?
are you a kid?
what did you make?
would you like to taste it?
-How is it? - A bit salty.
It's originally supposed to be salty.
What are you thinking about?
Am I the one cooking?
- Then do I have to do it? - We should do it together, since we both work.
It's a guys fantasy to have wife's food. I guess my fantasy is over
But you'll still cook for me, right?
I will cook 10 times over 10 year period
I guess it's going to be an annual event to enjoy your cooking
Are you getting married to get fed?
Who said that? I am saying there is some fun in that as well
your mother told me to prepare dowry well
what does she mean by well?
I don't know either. I am in a sticky situation too
You're a clever woman so I am sure you'll do well
This won't do
What won't do?
why?
you're so lovely
Where did you see such thing?
Don't ruin the moment
what should I do about the dowry?
It's good that your brain didn't get damaged.
- My head hurts though.
- I'll take care of you until you get better.
There are many people
that can take care of me.
Don't feel bad about me.
I can't believe I have to be his
servant until he gets better!
Eat it with this.
Why do you order food everyday?
What is it you want to say?
I know there's something you want to say to me. What is it?
mom, what's your budget for the wedding?
- I borrowed 100,000,000 won from the bank.
- 100,000,000 won?
Yeah, you should figure it out under 100,000,000 won.
You think we can buy all the wedding gifts and bottom drawers with that?
We can only buy the bottom drawers.
It won't cost that much.
What about the wedding gift?
You can just buy them nice comforters.
I know this man in Dong Dae Moon.
I can buy them at a very cheap price.
You aren't willing
to spend more, are you?
If I had more money, I would
spend it on housing stuff.
If they give you more than enough
wedding gifts, don't take them.
It's useless.
You sure know a lot of things, Mom.
Don't be sarcastic.
I'm also your father.
Did Mrs. Hae tell you to prepare good wedding gifts?
- No.
- Don't lie.
No. We just talked about Jung Hoon's
cousin's wedding and his families.
She must be so bored.
Anyway, if she talks about
the wedding gifts, tell me.
I think she's kind of greedy on that kind of stuff.
Don't get controlled by her.
Okay?
32,000,000 won. It's even less than the
bracelet that she bought for me last time.
What did she mean good wedding gifts?
What are you murmuring about?
What did you do for the wedding gifts?
I just gave them cash.
People these days usually do that.
How much did you do?
How much does your future house cost?
The gifts would depend on that.
I heard you should do 10% of how
much it costs to buy the house.
If the house is 200,000,000 won, then you
should give them about 20,000,000 won.
But it's hard to get a nice house
in Seoul with 200,000,000 won.
You know how much money
teachers can borrow from the bank?
- What's up?
- Can you talk on the phone?
Make it short.
- How's it going with our house?
- What house?
The house we're going to live.
Why are you telling me this now?
One of the teachers here said the wedding
gifts are dependent on the house.
I should know how much the house costs
so I can prepare for the gifts.
We decided to do it our own way.
Why are you listening to others?
I can't just ignore others.
Didn't I tell you that your mom wants
me to prepare good wedding gifts?
Am I getting married by myself?
Why are you so careless?
You called me and started talking
about the house suddenly.
I needed to know that for a reason.
What reason?
Never mind.
I gotta go.
She hung up on me again.
Here it is.
- You're borrowing 30,000,000 won, right?
- Yes.
You forgot to put your signature here.
Here is some soup.
What did you mean by good wedding gifts?
- Did Hae Yoon ask you that?
- Yeah.
These days, people give money as their
wedding gifts. I really hate that.
I see.
I want it to be something
that our family needs.
It's so hard. How does she know?
- Do you want me to make a list for her then?
- Sure.
I will do that so she won't feel pressure.
Mom, where am I going to live after I get married?
You said you're going to your hometown
with Dad after I get married.
Yeah. I was thinking of a studio.
30 Pyung at Chang Shin Dong.
You will actually have a 17
Pyung sized room to use.
Why is it Chang Shin Dong?
Hae Yoon's school is in Gang Book.
It'd be easy for her to work.
And my apartment will be empty after one year.
You guys can move in after that.
Then which one should I set up as a standard?
For what?
I don't know if the studio should be the standard
or the apartment should be the standard.
What do you mean?
I heard that the wedding gifts should be
10% of how much it costs for the house.
That's such a materialistic thought!
Does she want to impose a ceiling on
how much she can pay for the gifts?
Did she say she can't pay more than
10% of the costs for the house?
Why are you yelling at me? It's our first
time doing it so we're just asking you.
Fine. Let's do exactly half. Let's calculate
how much she has to pay for the gifts.
That's good for us anyway.
- Please calm down, Mom.
- I can't calm down!
Please be mature! Can't you do just
like how Ki Joong does for his wedding?
Why do you keep comparing me to him?
I will give you the apartment under the name
of you so the apartment is the standard.
Why are you doing this?
My arms are kind of fat. It looks
bad if I wear the wedding dress.
So where are we going to live?
They will give us a 33 Pyung sized
apartment in Chang Shin Dong.
Really?
But we have a problem.
What are you looking for?
It's so weird. I made stir-fried anchovies
and put them in here but it's gone.
I ate them all.
Did you eat them all?
It was a side dish.
Did you eat all of the tofu too?
Why are you checking the side dishes now
all of a sudden? I feel uncomfortable.
You got a boyfriend, didn't you?
No!
You look like a fickle cat.
You provide food and come home late.
Who is it?
I said I don't have one!
If you're dating a regular
guy, just live by yourself.
It's not good if you dated
a bad man at your age.
- You got a boyfriend?
- No. She's just saying it.
Why did Jung Hoon want to see you?
His mom said she will give us a 33 Pyung
sized apartment in Chang Shin Dong.
- What?
- That's good!
It's not good!
Is she going to give you an apartment
that's in Gang Book? That's it?
They're so cheap! Do they really
want to do that to their son?
I heard the wedding gifts should be the
10% of how much it costs for the house.
And people give them cash as a wedding gift.
What are you talking about?
There shouldn't be cash going back
and forth during the wedding.
She's so weird. I can't understand her.
I think I should talk to her.
Mom. Please. No. I'll do it.
What are you going to do? I know they
have a 45 Pyung sized apartment in Gang Nam.
They have an apartment in Gang Nam?
They do! You know, why did
I let you marry him?
Why do you think I let you marry
a guy who works at a toy company?
Please don't do it. Stay out of this. It
only gets worse, if you get involved.
There's nothing you can do
to make it better.
I did make it better. Who made
you have the wedding at a hotel?
It's all because of me...
If they find out you checked their
background, what will they think of us?
They'll think that we're very
conservative and careful about the wedding.
How can you have such
self-centered thinking?
Then should I only think of others?
I'll do everything about the gift and all.
So
please don't do anything. I'm begging you.
Just listen to her. It's her that's going to marry, not you.
You don't know because you don't have kids.
I can't just do nothing when I know it's not good for my kids.
You're growing well. Is this
how others get married too?
How come I can't contact him when I need him?
You came already?
You gave a job to a jobless.
I should come early.
Don't focus on the hall.
Focus on the kitchen.
Because it's for the press packet.
How much are you going to pay me?
Half as much you usually get paid by others.
You became very generous? Is it because
you're getting an engagement ceremony?
You didn't want to spend
money on me when we dated.
You're being sarcastic again.
Why
do we have to talk about that?
Because I don't understand why you
want to have that engagement ceremony.
If you keep doing this, we can't see each other.
Really? Your mouth tells me to go
away but your eyes tell me to come.
Ki Joong!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Have you heard from Min Ho?
I can't contact him.
- He got into an accident.
- When?
It's not salty enough.
What about rice?
Let's eat together.
You eat so well.
How long haven't you eaten?
I eat well actually.
I'll be done doing this after two more days.
Let's just be patient.
You're so mean. You're making food for
a patient.
What's so bad about that?
- Who got me hurt?
- Okay. I'm sorry.
Don't just say it. Show me how much you feel sorry.
There might be some aftereffects.
So you can't be so relieved.
Then how long do I have to do this?
Go open the door first.
Who is it?
It's Do Hyun. I'm in trouble
if he knows I'm here!
Why?
If my sister finds out I ride
a motorcycle, I'm so dead.
And Hae Jin will think that I'm not a moral and
ethical person at all since I'm with you alone.
You haven't experienced a man, have you?
You're a virgin, aren't you?
- No I'm not.
- Come here.
- Why?
- Come closer.
You really were a virgin!
- I'm patient!
- I can't believe you did this!
Why do I have to kiss
somebody I don't even love?
- Is this your first kiss?
- You bastard!
Do Hyun is coming.
What were you doing?
- Were you with a woman?
- No, no. I wasn't.
Let's go talk in my room.
- We can talk here.
- I was eating.
With the woman? Tell her to come out so I can say hi.
- There isn't a woman here.
- Sure. Then what's this?
A maid left that here.
Are you kidding me?
She
left shoes and this?
Your taste got worse.
If I said it's a maid's then it is a maid's.
Come here.
- Sit down.
- You're done eating.
Then let's have some coffee.
Who are you waving to?
Nobody.
- I must be really sick.
- No. It's just a scratch.
Why did you come here?
Why didn't you get the phone?
Do you
know how long I've been looking for you?
- Why?
- Have a seat.
Did something happen?
Min Ho, hold on to some of my properties.
Are you going to make a borrowed-name bank account?
I want to prepare for the future.
I want to be prepared for that.
You're the one I can trust the most.
Will you do that?
Sure. Why not?
I requested for provisional seizure.
Everything is going great.
Just wait to be fortunate.
What if he finds out about the seizure?
He won't unless he goes to get a registration.
But why would he do that?
If he tells you to put a house on sale, don't do it.
Did something go wrong again?
What is it now?
Hi, Mrs. Jung.
Time? Only lunch time.
Would you like to have lunch with me?
- You eat too.
- I will.
- Can you drink?
- Do you want to?
- What do you want to drink?
- Since we're having beef, soju will be good.
- Bring us a bottle of soju.
- Okay.
- Drink it.
If Hae Yoon's dad was alive, he could've
drank with you. That'd be nice.
Just think of me as her dad and mom.
I'm like a multiplayer.
From now, just think of me as her dad.
I will tell you man to man.
- About the house.
- Yeah.
Do you treat Hae Yoon with disdain?